A Guide to the Christian de Duve papers, Rockefeller University Faculty, Accession 2009:084 FA934
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, S-Z, 1985 (Box 14)
- Autograph Requests (Box 14)
- Job Applications (Box 14)
- Commitment Refusals (Box 14)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts or Scientific Techniques, etc. (Box 14)
- Interoffice Correspondence, University Bulletins (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, A-H, 1986 (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, J-R, 1986 (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, S-Z, 1986 (Box 14)
- Autograph Requests (Box 14)
- Commitment Refusals (Box 14)
- Job Applications (Box 14)
- Interoffice Correspondence, University Bulletins (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, A-I, 1987 (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, J-R, 1987 (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, S-Z, 1987 (Box 14)
- Commitment Refusals (Box 14)
- Autograph Requests (Box 14)
- Job Applications (Box 14)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Scientific Techniques, etc. (Box 14)
- Interoffice Correspondence, University Bulletins (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, A-I, 1988 (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, J-R, 1988 (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, S-Z, 1988 (Box 14)
- Nature Manuscript Submitted and Published (Box 14)
- Commitment Refusals (Box 14)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Scientific Techniques, etc. (Box 14)
- Autograph Requests (Box 14)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Interoffice Correspondence (Box 14)
- The Rockefeller University Senate (Box 14)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1989 (Box 15)
- Listeners' Guild, Incorporated (Box 15)
- Correspondence, A-I (Box 15)
- Correspondence, J-R (Box 15)
- Correspondence, S-Z (Box 15)
- Commitment Refusals (Box 15)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Scientific Techniques, etc. (Box 15)
- Autograph Requests, etc. (Box 15)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Interoffice Correspondence (Box 15)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1990 (Box 15)
- Correspondence, A-I (Box 15)
- Correspondence, J-R (Box 15)
- Correspondence, S-Z (Box 15)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Scientific Techniques, etc. (Box 15)
- Commitment Refusals (Box 15)
- Autograph Requests (Box 15)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Interoffice Correspondence (Box 15)
- Published in 1990: The Sciences and TIPS (Neil Patterson pubs.) (Box 15)
- TIPS (Box 15)
- Prelude to a Cell (The Sciences) (Box 15)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1991 (Box 15)
- Correspondence, S-Z (Box 15)
- Autograph Requests (Box 15)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Scientific Techniques, etc. (Box 15)
- Commitment Refusals (Box 15)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Interoffice Correspondence (Box 15)
- Correspondence, A-I (Box 15)
- Correspondence, J-R (Box 15)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1992 (Box 15)
- ICP (International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) Matters, 1992 (Box 15)
- ICP (International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) Business (Box 15)
- Neil Patterson/Sherri Foster/Morgan Ryan (Book of Life) (Box 15)
- Correspondence, A-I (Box 15)
- Correspondence, J-R (Box 15)
- Correspondence, S-Z (Box 15)
- Autograph Requests (Box 15)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Scientific Techniques, etc. (Box 15)
- Commitment Refusals (Box 15)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Interoffice Correspondence (Box 15)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1993 (Box 15)
- Correspondence, A-I (Box 15)
- Correspondence, J-R (Box 15)
- Correspondence, S-Z (Box 15)
- Commitment Refusals (Box 15)
- Correspondence on Manuscripts, Scientific Techniques, etc. (Box 15)
- Unanswered, Unsolicited Mail (Box 15)
- Autograph Requests (Box 15)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Interoffice Correspondence (Box 15)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1994 (Box 15)
- Neil Patterson (Box 15)
- Basic Books (Rabiner, etc.) (Box 15)
- Correspondence (Box 15)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Matters, Interoffice (Box 15)
- Commitment Refusals (Box 15)
- Autograph Request (Box 15)
- Unanswered, Unsolicited Mail (Box 15)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1995 (Box 16)
- General Correspondence (Box 16)
- Basic Books (Box 16)
- Neil Patterson (Box 16)
- Scientific American Correspondence (Box 16)
- American Scientist Correspondence re: Paper Appearing (Box 16)
- Commitment Refusals (Box 16)
- Autograph Requests (Box 16)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Matters, Interoffice (Box 16)
- Unanswered, Unsolicited Mail (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, 1996 (Box 16)
- Correspondence, A-L (Box 16)
- Correspondence, M-Z (Box 16)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Correspondence (Box 16)
- Autograph Requests (Box 16)
- Concerning Papers and Articles by Christian de Duve (Box 16)
- Unsolicited Mail (Box 16)
- Correspondence, 1997 (Box 16)
- Concerning Papers, Articles, etc. by Christian de Duve (Box 16)
- Correspondence, 1997 (Box 16)
- Autograph Requests (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, A-L (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, M-Z (Box 16)
- ICP (International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) Correspondence (Box 16)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Correspondence (Box 16)
- Unsolicited Mail (Box 16)
- Personal (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, A-L, 1998 (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, M-Z (Box 16)
- Correspondence re: Manuscripts, etc. (Box 16)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Correspondence (Box 16)
- Commitments, Declined (Box 16)
- Unsolicited Mail (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, A-L (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, M-Z (Box 16)
- Correspondence re: Manuscripts, etc. (Box 16)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Correspondence (Box 16)
- Unsolicited Mail (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, A-L, 2000 (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, M-Z, 2000 (Box 16)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Correspondence (Box 16)
- Correspondence re: Manuscripts, Books, etc. (Box 16)
- Unsolicited Mail (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, 2001 (Box 16)
- Correspondence, A-L (Box 16)
- Correspondence, M-Z (Box 16)
- Correspondence, ICP (International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) (Box 16)
- Correspondence re: Manuscripts, Books, etc. (Box 16)
- Unsolicited Mail (Box 16)
- Invitations (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, 2002 (Box 16)
- Correspondence, A-L (Box 16)
- Correspondence, M-Z (Box 16)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Correspondence (Box 16)
- ICP (International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) Correspondence (Box 16)
- Correspondence re: Manuscripts, Books, etc. (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, 2002 (Box 16)
- Invitations (Box 16)
- Unsolicited Mail (Box 16)
- General Correspondence, 2003 (Box 16)
- Correspondence, A-L (Box 16)
- Correspondence, M-Z (Box 16)
- Rockefeller University (RU) Correspondence (Box 16)
- ICP (International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) Correspondence (Box 16)
- Invitations, Requests (Box 16)
- Academie Pontificale des Sciences (Pontifical Academy of Sciences), 1968-1987 (Box 17)
- Academie Pontificale des Sciences (Pontifical Academy of Sciences), 1992-2001 (Box 17)
- Albert and Mary Lasker Foundation, 1970 (Box 17)
- American Academy for Arts and Sciences, 1971-2002 (Box 17)
- American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1977-1998 (Box 17)
- American Chemical Society, 1977-1990 (Box 17)
- American Philosophical Society, 1991-2003 (Box 17)
- American Society of Biological Chemists, 1980-1995 (Box 17)
- American Society for Cell Biology, 1973-1993 (Box 17)
- American Society for Cell Biology, 1963-1974 (Box 17)
- Assoc. pour la creation d'une Acad. Euro., 1978 (Box 17)
- Assoc. pour la diffusion des sciences, 1970 (Box 17)
- Mary Imogene Bassett Hospital, Advisory Council, 1970 (Box 17)
- Belgian-American Educational Foundation and Belgian-American Chamber of Commerce, 1971-1978 (Box 17)
- Biochemical Society, 1969-2003 (Box 17)
- Bioenergetics Advisory Group, 1971 (Box 17)
- British Society for Cell Biology, 1976 (Box 17)
- CNRS (Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique), 1965 (Box 17)
- Chaire Francqui, 1963-1968 (Box 17)
- CIBA Foundation, 1965-1972 (Box 17)
- Comité consultative de la recherché médicale (CCRM) de l'OMS, 1974-1975 (Box 17)
- Committee on the Impact of Biomedical Research, 1974-1975 (Box 17)
- Deutsche Akademie der Naturfurscher Leopoldina, 1973-1975 (Box 17)
- ECBO (European Cell Biology Organization), 1968-1972 (Box 17)
- EGSL (European Group for the Study of Lysosomes), 1969 (Box 17)
- FASEB, 1969-1987 (Box 17)
- FNRS (Fonds National de la Recherche Scientifique), 1964-1969 (Box 17)
- The Harvey Society, 1973-1976 (Box 17)
- Hôpital Francais Reine Elisabeth, Brussels, 1973-1976 (Box 17)
- HHMF (Howard Hughes Medical Foundation), 1971-1979 (Box 17)
- International Anatomy Congress, 1975 (Box 17)
- ICP (International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology), 1963-1983 (Box 18)
- Warner, Bradford (Box 18)
- ICP (International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) Correspondence (Box 18)
- ICP (International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology), 1993 (Box 18)
- RU-ICP (Rockefeller University-International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) Collaborative Program, Budget (Box 18)
- RU-ICP (Rockefeller University-International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) Program, 1977-1980 (Box 18)
- Harrelson, Allan, Rockefeller University Student (Box 18)
- Masquelier, Michele (Box 18)
- Beyer, Carl (Box 18)
- Emonds-Alt, Xavier (Box 18)
- Hoffmann-LaRoche Incorporated, John Burns (Box 18)
- Imperial Knife Associated Companies, Albert Baer (Box 18)
- Morgan Guarantee Trust Company, Robert F. Longley (Box 18)
- RU-ICP (Rockefeller University-International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) General (Box 18)
- RU-ICP (Rockefeller University-International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) Collaborative Program, 1970-1985 (Box 18)
- Old ICP (International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) Documents (Box 18)
- European-American Bank, Harry Ekblom and Andre Jacques (Box 18)
- Nichols, Rodney (Box 18)
- General Information (Box 18)
- News and Notes, 1977 December (Box 18)
- Chase Manhattan Bank, Michael W. Curran (Box 18)
- Technicon Corporation, Edwin C. Whitehead (Box 18)
- Van Hauwermeiren, M. Rene, Consul Général de Belgique (Box 18)
- Rockefeller University (RU) ICP (International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) Luncheon (Box 18)
- ICRO (International Cell Research Organization), 1965-1978 (Box 18)
- ICRO (International Cell Research Organization), Boston, 1976 September 11-12 (Box 18)
- ICRO (International Cell Research Organization), 1965-1978 (Box 18)
- L'Union Internationale de Biochimie (L'ICRO), Correspondence (Box 18)
- INSERM, 1975 (Box 18)
- International Union of Physiological Sciences (IUPS), 1965-1978 (Box 18)
- Board for the Definition of Terms, 1978 (Box 18)
- Commission on Cell Physiology (Box 18)
- International Union of Biochemistry, 1978-1979 (Box 18)
- International Virus Institute, India, 1971 (Box 18)
- Lysosome Club, 1965-1966 (Box 18)
- Lysosomotropic Chemotherapy, 1973-1975 (Box 18)
- Miscellaneous (Box 18)
- National Cancer Institute (Box 18)
- Farmitalia (Box 18)
- Lasker–Blair (Box 18)
- Merck, Sharp, Dohme, Research Laboratories, 1976-1981 (Box 18)
- Mellon Foundation, 1976-1978 (Box 18)
- National Academy of Sciences, 1975-1988 (Box 18)
- National Institute on Alcohol Abuse and Alcoholism, 1975 (Box 18)
- National Institutes of Health, 1963-1978 (Box 18)
- New York Academy of Sciences, 1970-2002 (Box 18)
- New York Hall of Science, Biology Advisory Panel, 1986-2002 (Box 18)
- Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association Foundation Fellowship, 1977-1980 (Box 18)
- Public Health Service, 1963 (Box 18)
- Radio-Télévision Belge, 1973 (Box 18)
- Reticuloendothelial Society, 1972 (Box 18)
- Research on Disease (ROD), 1975-1980 (Box 18)
- Rockefeller University (RU) ICP (International Institute of Cellular and Molecular Pathology) Parasitology Program, 1977 (Box 18)
- Smithsonian Institutionf (Box 18)
- Societe Belge de Biologie Cellulaire, 1976 (Box 18)
- Société de Biologie, France, 1976 (Box 19)
- Société de Chimie Biologique, 1963-1976 (Box 19)
- World Health Organization (WHO), 1977-1978 (Box 19)
- PNAS (Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences), Papers Submitted, 1981-1989 (Box 19)
- Miscellaneous PNAS (Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences) Reviews (Box 19)
- Manuscript Refusals and General PNAS (Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences) Correspondence (Box 19)
- Willard-Gallo, Van de Keere, Kettmann: "Helper T-cells Infected With HIV-1 Downmodulate" (Box 19)
- PNAS (Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences), M. I. Darville, K. M. Crepin, L. Hue, and G. G. Russo, 1989 (Box 19)
- PNAS (Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences), 1988-1999 (Box 19)
- Yukio, Fujiki, PNAS (Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences) Paper (Box 19)
- Yukio, PNAS (Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences), Construire la Cellule (Box 19)
- Rifkin and Landsberger, "Trypanosome Variant Surface Glucoprotein.…" (Box 19)
- Coppens, Baudhuin, Opperdoes and Courtoy (Box 19)
- Requests to Purchase Equipment, 1977-1979 (Box 19)
- Requests to Purchase Equipment, 1975-1982 (Box 19)
- 68-02-2420 (Box 19)
- Correspondence on Purchase of NSF (National Science Foundation) Equipment (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation) Comparative Biochemistry of Subcellular Oganelles: PCM-8008713, 1980 October 1-1984 March 31 (Box 19)
- Final Report (Box 19)
- PCM-8008713-03 (Box 19)
- Progress Report, 1982 (Box 19)
- Progress Report, NSF (National Science Foundation) PCM8008713, Sent 1981 April 10 (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation) PCM 8309294: Comparative Biochemistry of Subcellular Oganelles:, 1983 December 1-1986 May 31 (Box 19)
- Final Report on PCM 76-16657, 1976-1981 (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation), Energy Metabolism of Hydrogenosomes, 811-0606, Miklos Müller, 1981-1982 (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation) Research Proposal for Specialized Research Equipment, Spectophotometer…PB Lazarow, 1977 (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation) Grant, PCM 76-16657, 1976 October 1-1981 March 31 (Box 19)
- PCM 76-16657-04 (Box 19)
- PCM 76-16657-03 (Box 19)
- PCM 76-16657-02 (Box 19)
- PCM 76-16657-01, 1976 October 1-1977 September 30 (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation) Grant, GB-26222 Electron Microscope, 1970-1972 (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation) Grant, BMS72-02224 A03 (Formerly GB-35258X), 1972-1977 (Box 19)
- Progress Reports, BMS 72-02224 (Formerly GB-35258X) (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation) Grant, BMS72-02224 A03 (Formerly GB-35258X), 1972-1977 (Box 19)
- Correspondence, BMS 72-02224 A03 (GB-35258X) (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation) Grant, BMS 72-02224 A03, 1975 September 1-1976 August 1 (Box 19)
- BMS 72-02224, 1972 May 1-1977 April 30 (Box 19)
- 76-16657, 1976 September 1-1981 August 31 (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation) BMS 72-02224 (Final Report) (Box 19)
- Application for Supplement to NSF (National Science Foundation) Grant GB-5796X, 1970-1972 (Box 19)
- Grant Application, GB 5796X (Box 19)
- Application for Supplement to GB 5796X, 1972 (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation) Grant Application, 1971 (Box 19)
- Application for Supplement to GB 5796X, 1970-1971 (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation) Grant GB 5796X, 1967-1972 (Box 19)
- Application (Box 19)
- GB 5796X, Decision Letter, 1967 March 1-1969 February 29 (Box 19)
- Correspondence GB 5796X (Box 19)
- NSF (National Science Foundation)GB 5796X, Progress Reports (Box 19)
- Budget Proposals and Interim Reports (National Science Foundation (NSF) #GB5796X) (Box 19)
- GB 5796X Statements (Box 19)
- Notice of Grant Award (Supplement), 1972 May 1-August 31 (Box 19)
- National Science Foundation (NSF), GB-3621, 1965-1972 (Box 20)
- Decisions (Box 20)
- Statements. GB-3621 (Box 20)
- Applications, GB-3621 (Box 20)
- Correspondence (Box 20)
- National Science Foundation (NSF), GB-2871, 1964-1967 (Box 20)
- GB-2871, Applications (Box 20)
- Correspondence, GB-2871 (Box 20)
- Decision, GB-2871 (Box 20)
- Statements (Box 20)
- National Science Foundation (NSF), GB-588, 1962-1964 (Box 20)
- Correspondence (Box 20)
- Final Report (Box 20)
- Statements (Box 20)
- Applications (Box 20)
- National Science Foundation (NSF), General Correspondence, 1964 (Box 20)
- International Travel Grant Application (Box 20)
- Grant Applications, Documentation Center, 1965-1966 (Box 20)
- Applications (Box 20)
- Information (Box 20)
- Proposals (Box 20)
- Correspondence (Box 20)
- Oak Ridge, Union Carbide Contract, 1967-1976 (Box 20)
- Fogarty International Center, 1971-1977 (Box 20)
- Lab Expansion Plans, 1969-1977 (Box 20)
- Plans to Increase Lab Space (Box 20)
- Correspondence, Lab Expansion (Box 20)
- Lab Rebuilding (Box 20)
- Lab Extension (Box 20)
- Laboratory Rebuilding (Box 20)
- Biomedical Research Support Grant (BRSG), RR-07065 (M. Müller) (Box 20)
- Weizmann Institute/Rockefeller University (RU) Collaboration (Box 20)
- Irma T. Hirschel Career Scientist Award Application (Carl Beyer), 1978 (Box 20)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) Training Grant for Pathobiology, Application for Rockefeller University (RU), G. Blobel, Investigator, 1975-1985 (Box 20)
- Müller, Miklos, Program Director, National Institute Health (NIH) Training Parasitology Grant, 1980 (Box 20)
- Prophet Grant Application, 1980-1983 (Box 20)
- Perkins, Margaret, National Institute of Health (NIH) AI-19585: (Plasmodium Falciparum Invasion of Human Erythrocytes), 1983-1985 (Box 20)
- American Cancer Society, Carl Beyer, 1980-1981 (Box 20)
- American Heart Association, Grant Application (Fowler), 1976-1979 (Box 20)
- New York Heart Association, S. Fowler, 1976-1979 (Box 20)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) Cytopathology of Atherosclerosis, S. Fowler, HL-24229, 1980 July 1-1982 June 30 (Box 20)
- LaBadie, "Cell Surface in Lymphocyte-Mediated Cytotoxicity", AI-15867, 1979-1982 (Box 20)
- New York Heart Association Fellowship, Paul Lazarow, 1980-1986 (Box 20)
- New York Heart Association, Grant Application (P. Lazarow), 1981 (Box 20)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) AM 19394-01, "Biogenesis of Rat Liver Peroxisomes", Paul B. Lazarow, 1976-1982 (Box 20)
- HL-18157 (Box 20)
- HL-18157-6, Subcellular Events in Atherosclerosis, 1980 June 1-1981 May 31 (Box 20)
- HL-18157-5, Subcellular Events in Atherosclerosis, 1979 June 1-1980 May 31 (Box 20)
- HL-18157-5, Summary Statement (Box 20)
- HL-18157-5, Requests to Purchase Equipment (Box 20)
- HL-18157-4 (Box 20)
- HL-18157-3 (Box 20)
- HL-18157-2 (Box 20)
- HL-18157-1 (Box 20)
- HL-18157, Renewal Application, 1981 (Box 20)
- National Institute of Health (NIH) HL-18157 (Various Correspondence), 1976-1983 (Box 20)
- HL-18157-07 (Box 20)
- Requests to Transfer Funds (Box 20)
- Subcellular Events in Atherosclerosis, Renewal Application (Box 20)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 20)
- Permission to Use Human Tissues (Box 20)
- Poole, National Institute of Health (NIH) 1ROi AG 00609, "Protein Degradation, Lysosome Function and Senescence", 1977-1982 (Box 20)
- Extinct Grants and Fellowships, 1976-1978 (Box 21)
- Harrison, E. H., Fellowship Continuation Application, "Membrane Dynamics of Cytotoxic T-lymphocytes" (Box 21)
- Haley, Nancy Jean (Box 21)
- "Subcellular Pathology of Human Atheroma", P. Berberian (Box 21)
- Whitehall Foundation Grant Application, Miklos Müller, 1980 August-1981 (Box 21)
- Whitehall Foundation, Miklos Müller, "Bioenergetics of Hydrogenosomes", 1981 February 25 (Box 21)
- Lazarow, National Institute of Health (NIH) HL 20909, "Clofibrate-Enhanced Lipid Oxidation by Peroxisomes", 1977-1980 (Box 21)
- Venereal Diseases Research Fund, Application for Research Training Fellowship, Tom Gorrell, 1979 (Box 21)
- AI 11942-01, Müller, 1974 January 1-1977 December 31 (Box 21)
- AI 11942-07 (Miklos Müller) (Box 21)
- AI 11942-04 (Box 21)
- AI 11942- (Box 21)
- Renewal AI 11942, Biochemical Cytology of T. vag. (Box 21)
- AI 11942-01 (Box 21)
- World Health Organization, Grant Application Reviews, 1974 (Box 21)
- Confidential Character and Job Application Evaluations, 1977-Present, 1982-1984 (Box 21)
- Confidential, 1976, Character References, Recommendations, Application Evaluations (alphabetical) (Box 21)
- Confidential, 1975, Character References, Recommendations, Application Evaluations (alphabetical) (Box 21)
- Goldman, Rachel (Box 21)
- Schuel, Herbert (Box 21)
- Confidential, 1970-1974, Character References, Recommendations, Application Evaluations (alphabetical) (Box 21)
- Confidential, 1963-1969, Character References, Recommendations, Application Evaluations (alphabetical) (Box 21)
- EMBO (European Molecular Biology Organization), 1964-1971 (Box 21)
- Conférence Européenne de Biologie Moléculaire (Box 21)
- Bristol-Myers Squibb Award, 1997-2003 (Box 21)
- Boon, Thierry (Box 21)
- Boon, Thierry (Box 21)
- Gairdner Foundation, 1967-1984 (Box 21)
- Gairdner Prize, 1967 (Box 21)
- Gairdner Foundation Dinner (magnetic tape), 1967 November 17 (Box 21)
- Gairdner Foundation Dinner (magnetic tape), 1963 November 29 (Box 21)
- Herman and Ruth Goodman Foundation, 1974-1976 (Box 22)
- Heineken Prize, 1975-1989 (Box 22)
- Hoffmann-La Roche Incorporated, 1975 (Box 22)
- V. D. Mattia Award, 1985-1992 (Box 22)
- Lasker Nominations, 1984-2002 (Box 22)
- MacArthur Foundation Nominations, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
- Nobel Chemistry, 1996-2000 (Box 22)
- Nobel Chemistry, 1999 (Box 22)
- Nobel Chemistry, 1998 (Box 22)
- Nobel Chemistry, 1996-1997 (Box 22)
- Nobel Chemistry, 1995 (Box 22)
- Nobel Chemistry, 1994 (Box 22)
- Nobel Nominations for Chemistry, 1970-1973 (Box 22)
- Nobel Physiology or Medicine, 1993-1999 (Box 22)
- Nobel Physiology or Medicine, 1999 (Box 22)
- Nobel Physiology or Medicine, 1997-1998 (Box 22)
- Nobel Physiology or Medicine, 1993-1996 (Box 22)
- Nobel Physiology or Medicine, 1976-1992 (Box 22)
- Nobel Physiology or Medicine, 1986-1992 (Box 22)
- Nobel Physiology or Medicine, 1976-1985 (Box 22)
- Nobel Peace Nomination, 1977 (Box 22)
- Miscellaneous Nominations, 1985 (Box 22)
- National Medal of Science, 1976-1986 (Box 22)
- Prix Quinquennal, 1966-1979 (Box 22)
- de Duve, Christian, Curriculum Vitae and Bibliography (Box 23)
- de Duve, Christian, Bibliography, 1981 (Box 23)
- Curriculum Vitae, French (Box 23)
- Annotated Bibliography (Box 23)
- Bibliography (Box 23)
- Curriculum Vitae, English (Box 23)
- Personal, 1964-1973 (Box 23)
- de Duve, Christian, Biography (Box 23)
- Air Canada (Box 23)
- Accident, Johnson and Higgins (Box 23)
- Personal Information (Box 23)
- Bibliography (Complete), 1992 (Box 23)
- Marquis Who's Who (Box 23)
- American Men and Women of Science, 1997 (Box 23)
- Other Who's Who (British Publications), 1993 (Box 23)
- Blobel, Gunter, 1989-1996 (Box 23)
- Hers (Box 23)
- Character References and Nominations, 1976-1985 (Box 23)
- Brady, Roscoe (Box 23)
- Chance, Britton (Box 23)
- Hayaishi, O. (Box 23)
- Mitchell, Peter (Box 23)
- Palade, George (Box 23)
- Racker, Efraim (Box 23)
- Straus, Werner (Box 23)
- Brown, Michael S. and Joseph L. Goldstein, 1984 (Box 23)
- Gross Horowitz Prize, 1969, 1985 (Box 23)
- Gairdner Nominations, 1991-2000 (Box 23)
- Boon, Thierry (Box 23)
- Hirsch, James and Zanvil Cohn, Gairdner Foundation, International Award, 1978 (Box 23)
- General Information (Box 23)
- Extant Non-Faculty, Katrie (Karrie) Polowetzky, 1997-2004 (Box 24)
- Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 24)
- Correspondence, 2001 (Box 24)
- Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 24)
- Correspondence, 1998 (Box 24)
- Correspondence, 1997 (Box 24)
- Extant Non-Faculty, Katrie (Karrie) Polowetzky, 1994-1996 (Box 24)
- Extant Non-Faculty, Katrie (Karrie) Polowetzky, 1996 (Box 24)
- Extant Non-Faculty, Katrie (Karrie) Polowetzky, 1995-1996 (Box 24)
- Extant Non-Faculty, Katrie (Karrie) Polowetzky, 1994 (Box 24)
- Extant Non-Faculty, Katrie (Karrie) Polowetzky, 1974-1999 (Box 24)
- Extant Non-Faculty, Katrie (Karrie) Polowetzky, 1993 (Box 24)
- Polowetzky, Anna (Box 24)
- Polowetzky (Box 24)